Andrew Le

andrewle713@gmail.com ❖ (310) 953-5958 ❖ Santa Ana, CA

Dedicated and driven university student with a specialization in Information at University of California Irvine's Donald Bren School of Information & Computer Sciences. Advocate for redefining and broadening digital accessibility across social backgrounds and minority communities. Eager and enthusiastic team member ready to join companies and organizations that promote an inclusive and informed future.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Her Idea Oct. 2021 – Jan. 2022

Web Developer Intern

Remote/ San Francisco Bay Area, CA

- Assisted in the design and implementation of heridea.org to promote the non-profit's digital outreach and engagement.
- Actively researched and implemented SEO techniques to boost website visits.
- Summarized website status updates in weekly team meetings to further boost website traffic.

American Red Cross Aug. 2019 – June 2020

Activities Coordinator Volunteer

Redondo Beach, CA

- Managed and facilitated a 5 person team to schedule and execute club activities and events.
- Presented new outreach strategy research and club activity progress at monthly district general meetings.
- Spearheaded fundraiser campaign in support of initiative to fight against Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) by contacting and coordinating with local businesses; producing and distributing marketing materials.

EDUCATION

University of California, Irvine

Sep. 2020 - June 2024

Irvine, CA

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

SKILLS & INTERESTS

- Technical Skills:
 - o **Programming Languages:** Python, C++, Java, JavaScript/HTML/CSS, SQL
 - o **Tools:** Git, Linux, AWS (EC2), Maven
 - o Applications: MS Word, MS Excel
- Soft Skills: Communication, Critical Thinking, Teamwork, Organization, Resourceful, Time Management
- Interests: Photography, Video Editing, PC-Building, Guitar, Video Games

PROJECTS

File Management System

- Cross-platform program that creates and deletes user profiles
- Ability to search for, delete and read files (within a directory) on user's local storage system
- Features allow program connection to and utilization of weather and music API, obtaining and interpreting ISON formatted data that is transcribed onto a file

Fabflix

- Web application allowing users to login to the site, browse and search for movies, and add movies to a cart
- Utilizes JavaScript/HTML/CSS, Java and SQL while maintaining front-end to back-end separation
- Searching and browsing includes sorting and pagination features